# LAURA DE BORBÓN **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**



#### PERSONAL DETAILS

Argentine, Italian

Dungarvan, Co. Waterford, Ireland

+353 85 737 2436

✓ laudebor@gmail.com

lin

linkedin.com/in/laudebor

github.com/laudebor

#### **PROFILE**

Studious, responsible, fast learner, passionate about technology, collaborative, teamwork. Experience developing Web APIs as a team, both backend and full stack. Technologies applied: Spring Boot, Java, Hibernate, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Thymeleaf, Git, among others.

Experience developing web database applications with Caspio.

Mathematical education and skills like problem solving, logic and critical thinking.

## **SKILLS**

- JAVA
- SPRING BOOT
- MYSQL
- HTML, CSS
- CASPIO
- MATHEMATICS AND LOGIC
- SOLVING PROBLEMS
- CRITICAL THINKING

## **LANGUAGES**

- Spanish: native level.
- · English: advanced level.

## **API WEB PROJECTS**

RESTful Java Backend API for a fictional NGO (Skill Up).

Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Junit5, Mockito, Swagger. Repository at github.com/laudebor/ONG-API-Java-Backend.

RESTful Java Backend API to manage Disney movies (Skill Up Entrance Challenge). Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, MySQL. Repository at github.com/laudebor/Preaceleracion-deBorbon-Laura

Full Stack API Web to make surveys (course final project). Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, HTML, CSS, Thymeleaf, MySQL. Repository at github.com/laudebor/AMQApp

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Tech Consultant, Internship at Fendous Sustainable Solutions, Denmark, From March to June 2023, Responsible for the development and design of database web applications using the Caspio platform for the backend, and HTML and CSS for the frontend. Creation of documentation. testing and production of content.

Mathematics University Professor. Head of Practical Works. FCE - UNCuyo. Subject: Math I (linear algebra). From March 2019 to June 2023. Teaching classes, production of practical works, correcting exams, among other tasks.

Professor of the pre-university Math Module. FCE - UNCuyo. Year 2019. Teaching classes and correcting exams.

# WEB DEVELOPMENT TRAINING

Skill Up Java Backend. Alkemy, Argentina. Issue: October 2022. Technologies: Java, Spring Boot, Spring Security, Hibernate, MySQL, JUnit5, Mockito, Swagger, Cit, IntelliJ IDEA, Postman, among others.

Full Stack Web Programming Course. Egg Company, Argentina. From August 2021 to June 2022. Basic content: Java, Object-Oriented Programming, MySQL, JPA, Spring Boot, Thymeleaf, HTML, CSS.

#### **EDUCATION**

PhD in Mathematical Sciences. Graduated from FCFMyN-UNSL, San Luis, Argentina. From 2018 to 2022. Qualification: Outstanding.

Master's degree in Mathematics. Graduated from FCFMyN-UNSL, San Luis, Argentina. From 2018 to 2021. Qualification: Outstanding.

Mathematics degree. Licenciatura with thesis. Graduated from FCEN-UNCuyo, Mendoza, Argentina. From 2013 to 2018. Qualification: 9.69/10.

# **DISTINCTIONS**

**CONICET Internal Doctoral Scholarship**. Year 2018. Gold Medal to the best graduated of FCEN - UNCuyo. Academic Average 9.69 on a scale from 0 to 10. Year 2018.

First National Flag Escort of FCEN - UNCuyo. Year 2017.